There is another lady. For five years, she has been having difficulty in walking
due to osteoarthritis of the right knee
She is using a knee brace.
Come on. Remove it.
Ministration Of Healing And Deliverance
In Jesus' Name
Come here! Don't go.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Don't go. This is suicide.
This is suicide spirit.
Yes, I have been trying to commit suicide.
This is a snake. You people worship snake.
Yes, sir.
Ministration Of Prophecy And Deliverance
In Jesus' Name
They call it 'mother' when the snake is passing my place.
They call the snake 'mamma' when it is coming; they don't kill it.
Come here! That is another snake there.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
There are three here.
Ministration Of Prophecy And Deliverance
In Jesus' Name
There is another - two - putting on blue.
Ministration Of Prophecy And Deliverance
In Jesus' Name
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Remaining one.
Come here. Bring him.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Ministration Of Prophecy And Deliverance
In Jesus' Name
- You are a medical doctor.
- Yes, sir. I am, sir.
- You want to jump off...
- ...the bridge. Sometimes in the hospital...
- Off the bridge?
- Yes, sir.
Sometimes, I want to infuse myself with an infusion that can cause cardiac arrest.
On several times, I tried to commit suicide.
Take it easy. Sometimes, you want to jump off the bridge.
Yes, sir. I can feel an aura when it comes, suggesting to me to take my life.
Ok, leave the road. You will see.
You will see what we are talking about now. Leave that place.
Ministration Of Prophecy And Deliverance
In Jesus' Name
That is the spirit - instant reaction as the man of God has said.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
The man of God said that spirit, that suicidal spirit will manifest
and that is what we are seeing right now.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
- You wanted to do what?
- I wanted to kill him on Wednesday.
He now touched Emmanuel TV.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Who are you?
Idol of the family.
"Who are you?" - you will do that later.
Will you allow me to deliver him?
Leave this man!
Come on. Leave him; it's alright.
Who are you? - okay.
Ministration Of Prayer And Deliverance
In Jesus' Name
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Watch your screen. Three of them delivered at the same time.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I'm free! Thank You, Jesus! I'm free; I'm delivered!
TT: Mel Flowers 28/04/2019